{
    "subject": "Zak_Penn",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "The_Grand__film_",
    "human_readable": "Zak Penn created the film The Grand.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8402737379074097,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Zak Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7863627672195435,
            "question": "Who created the film The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7055185437202454,
            "question": "Are there any other films created by Zak Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5180413126945496,
            "question": "Is Zak Penn a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4244598150253296,
            "question": "Has Zak Penn won any awards for his work on The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3273743987083435,
            "question": "What is the plot of The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30198583006858826,
            "question": "What genre is the film The Grand likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2564113438129425,
            "question": "What year was The Grand released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22129838168621063,
            "question": "Who stars in The Grand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14972510933876038,
            "question": "Where can one watch The Grand?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zak Penn created the film The Grand.",
            "html": "yago_8436_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who stars in The Grand?",
            "html": "yago_8436_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was The Grand released?",
            "html": "yago_8436_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film The Grand likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_8436_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8436_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Zak Penn created the film The Grand. The document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8436/re-ranker-msmarco/82.txt mentions that \"Zak Penn's second feature as a director, The Grand, is getting only the smallest of releases...\" and another document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8436/re-ranker-msmarco/90.txt states that \"Zak Penn\u2019s poker comedy mockumentary now has a domestic distributor as Anchor Bay Entertainment has acquired all the North American rights to his film The Grand which he both wrote and directed.\" These mentions indicate that Zak Penn was involved in creating the film The Grand, either by directing or writing it."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly indicate that Zak Penn both wrote and directed the film \"The Grand.\" Therefore, the triple stating that Zak Penn created the film \"The Grand\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}